let's look at the answer to our cache
line quiz the cache tag always contains
the entire address of the first byte we
know this is not true the address that
we supply to the cache on an Access
contains the offset and the block number
we have seen that the tag only needs to
contain the block number part not the
offset the block always begins at an
aligned address so the first byte of the
block actually always have zero here so
there is no need to store those zeros in
the cache as a tag the tag only needs to
give us the bits that we need to
identify the block the bits that we know
are always zero are not necessary so
this is definitely not true it contains
at least one bit from the block offset
again this is not true we need only the
bits that tell us which block we have
the block offset tells us where are we
within a particular block so these bits
are never necessary that also means that
this is not true however the tag does
contain at least one bit from the block
number we have seen in our example that
the entire block number can be a tag in
that particular cache in general it
might be fewer than all of the bits but
there is at least one of them so this is
the only correct answer